[Music]
do
it is a warm sunny spring morning here
the birds are so talkative right now
busy finding mates and making plans for
the warmer months it feels like nature's
symphony outdoors
as you can see i recently found this
very sweet sewing box while shopping at
a secondhand store
one of the legs was broken but could
easily be fixed and so i got it on a
good deal
while i will not use it for sewing it
accommodates all my art supplies really
well if you're a crafter artist you
understand how a box that properly
organizes all your things is a treasure
[Music]
i've actually spent some time shopping
in the nearby town recently which feels
strange because i don't really spend
much time out of my valley much less
purchasing items from my home
it's very exciting and feels very
different my fiance has encouraged me to
really make this place feel cozy and
even though i was only looking for a
couple thrifted items i did find some
cute little knick-knacks
i also received some lovely gifts from
you and some family members in
celebration of the housewarming
thank you all of it has been so
comforting during this shift in my life
[Music]
do
one of my favorite low-budget ways to
decorate is just to decorate with books
you can find interesting looking books
almost anywhere secondhand for very
little cost
i like to get ones that i'm both
interested to read but also others that
just speak to me
their covers may be intricate or the
stories that are told can teach me
something about the people who lived in
the past and their perception of the
world
next time you go to a thrift store maybe
look out for some fun books within a
specific color scheme or style
i find it always adds something really
unique to the space and you can usually
get a lot for very little if you keep an
eye out for deals
[Music]
so far i don't think there's any secret
to decorating a space in a very inviting
and unique way
except that it takes time over the
course of years instead of being in a
rush you can find so many fun and
interesting things that are both
affordable and can be easily repurposed
or upcycled
i have kind of just ended up putting all
my plants and some of my favorite things
in this corner because there is a lot of
still
construction renovations going on in the
other part of the house you could
probably see i i'll have to turn the
camera but there is
um a doorway being cut into this wall
because the stairs from the first floor
are going to meet this floor and that is
where
luke's father is working on it today so
it's
a lot of things happening in the house
still so it definitely is a space of
transition and a little bit of chaos
right now which is
really exciting and wonderful and
it's starting to feel like we are
getting really close to having a more
completed home and it has been so
beautiful to see how hard luke's father
and luke have been working on the space
i did get really excited the other day
though because i went to an antique shop
because i was looking for
a rug for the back room
and i found a
old vintage ice cream maker which
is really exciting my my eyes looked at
it right now i actually have it right
over there it is a beautiful kind of
green color and it is
in very good condition on the inside and
so i'm really excited next week to try
to make some different types of ice
cream because
definitely if i'm ever in a time of
great change and many emotions ice cream
usually resolves
95 of it
so i'm very excited to try out some new
ice cream recipes and share the process
with you it'll definitely be an
experiment because i have never used a
vintage ice cream maker before but i'm
excited to learn anyway about a month or
two ago i asked for questions on
instagram first there was some more
personal questions one was
um
how are preparations for the wedding
going you know i actually have to say so
far
there have been challenging sometimes a
little bit stressful times in the
process of planning but overall the
wedding is going to be very small and
very simple and it's actually going to
be on a little farm
not too far away from here and it's
going to be a lovely sweet little venue
and it has
not been too hard to plan but there's
always those moments where you feel a
little bit overwhelmed but yeah
definitely keeping it simple has really
helped yeah we're we're very excited
it's just going to be very close family
and i think it will be absolutely
beautiful because it will be in may and
there's going to be so many beautiful
flowers out and we're going to have a
little local string quartet come and
play as well
and yeah it's gonna be a beautiful day
so far it has not been too stressful but
we also are still a ways away so that
may change i have already found my dress
i found it for a few hundred dollars at
a little
wedding boutique when i went to visit my
sister in houston she and i went to go
a wedding dress shopping because she
loves that experience and i wasn't so
sure but i ended up enjoying it very
much as well
and yes i found a sweet simple little
dress i don't know if it was meant to be
a bridesmaid dress or a
actual wedding dress and it has
embroidery on it as well which i really
liked and it had some floral elements so
i will no doubt show you at a future
point i noticed there are some new
people here recently so feel free to
introduce yourselves in the comments and
tell us what country you're from i
always think that's really exciting to
see all the different places people
around the world are
tuning in from it's always really
interesting and i think it has a very
lovely way of bringing us all together
sadly my microphone briefly stopped
working while filming this but i still
wanted to wish you a lovely week
and i will see you very soon and i'm
sending my love
[Music]
you